

Gracie Lundell

Junior Web Developer in Portland, OR

(971) 322 - 3400

gracielundell@gmail.com

http://github.com/gracielundell

http://linkedin.com/in/gracielundell

http://gracielundell.com

Technical SI	CILLS	5
CSS/Sass		

JavaScript jQuery

HTML5

Git

Frameworks

Ember.js Angular 2.0

Bootstrap

Design Skills

SketchApp

Wireframing/Prototyping

UX/UI

InVision

Mobile-first/Responsive design

Atomic Design

PROJECTS

GROW — *Gardening App* (https://projects.invisionapp.com/share/AN7B6QM86#/screens) MAY 2016

An app designed to help backyard farmers track their garden's progress, with journal and calendar features. The app was wireframed and designed using SketchApp. Functionality was added through the web application, InVision. Being a solo project, I designed everything myself, from the wireframes, to the InVision final version.

Scout — *Social Media App* (https://projects.invisionapp.com/share/W77DULQ3G#/screens) MAY 2016

This app's goal is to help people explore new cities through scavenger hunt-like activities. The role I played in the team was to examine user-experience, determining what aspects would be most appreciated by users. I also designed the app's main logo, color scheme, and user flow. It was given functionality through InVision.

EXPERIENCE

 ${\bf Black\ Tower\ Entertainment} -- {\it Remote\ Intern}$

JUNE 2016 - JULY 2016

A five-week internship where I focused on CSS/Sass and Ember.js for the soon-to-be released web game, *Iron Vice*. My responsibilities included managing and implementing the redesign for the lobby menu page, including wireframes, working with the client to understand their vision, writing Sass, and converying information between components using Handlebars.

 $\textbf{Ruby Jewel,} \ \textbf{Portland,} \ \textbf{OR} - \textit{Catering Staff}$

MAY 2013 - SEPTEMBER 2015

Member of the catering staff. Responsibilities included packing all equipment and product for events, as well as driving the delivery van and dropping off and picking up supplies for other members of the staff.

EDUCATION

Epicodus, Portland, Or *Front-end Web Design*JANUARY 2016 - JULY 2016

A vocational school for junior software developers where I studied JavaScript with a focus on CSS, Web Design, and User Experience for front-end web development. I gained pair-programming skills as well, and learned how to better communicate ideas to others.

Portland Community College, Portland, Or

Associate's Degree in General Studies SEPTEMBER 2012 - JUNE 2015

GPA: 3.5